Ahmed Shahin

El-Bâgûr, Monufia, Egypt (GMT+2)

) +20 1558389586

<u>shahinforwork@gmail.com</u>

• https://github.com/shahinovic

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ahmed-shahin-64ba80256/

Summary

Hello there, My name is Ahmed Shahin, I'm a React.js Frontend Web Developer who has 1+ years of work experience in the industry of frontend web development, I enjoy building everything with JavaScript. In this duration, I have learned a lot of technologies, created many cool websites, collaborated with great developers and contributed to open source

projects.
So I'm always seeking to have an opportunity that matches my skills, to make the best use of all what I have learned.

Skills

> HTML5

> JavaScript (ES6)

> Bootstrap

> React.js

> CSS3

> JSON

> SASS

> Redux & Redux toolkit

Languages

> Arabic - native

> English - Intermediate

Experience

> Intern2grow - Remote

React Developer - internship

April 2023 - April 2023

> Intern2grow - Remote

UI Developer - internship

March 2023 - March 2023

> Intern2grow - Remote

Javascript Developer - Internship

February 2023 - February 2023

Education

> Student in Faculty of Law

Menofia university - Menofia - Egypt

Projects

> My Portfolio

That's my personal website where I show my skills and projects.

- Built with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, JSON, React.js
- View at https://portfolio-6f54ou3it-shahinovic.vercel.app

> marketing-website

This is a marketing website, The website showcases various products and allows users to add items to their cart.

- Built using Vite, React.js, Redux, and Redux Toolkit.
- View at https://marketing-website-chi-ten.vercel.app/

> computer-engineering

This is a computer engineering app, The app provides various features and information related to computer engineering.

- Built using Vite, React.js, Redux,Bootstrap, React-Bootstrap, and Redux Toolkit.
- View at https://computer-engineering.vercel.app/

> Crytoverse

CryptoVerse is a web application designed for cryptocurrency traders and enthusiasts. It provides real-time updates on cryptocurrency prices, market trends, and news, as well as advanced tools for technical analysis and social features for community building.

- Built with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, React.js, antd, chart.js, millify, moment, @reduxjs/toolkit
- View at https://crytoverse-six.vercel.app

> Wikipedia Search Engine

The Wikipedia Search Engine is a web-based tool that allows users to search for specific content within the vast database of Wikipedia. It uses advanced algorithms to retrieve and display relevant information based on user input. Users can search using keywords, phrases, or sentences to quickly access articles and other content on a wide range of topics.

- Built with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, JSON
- View at https://shahinovic.github.io/wikipedia-search-engine

> Excel Sheet Generator

This is a simple Excel sheet generator web application that allows users to create and download Excel spreadsheets with custom data.

- Built with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6, JSON
- View at https://shahinovic.github.io/excel-sheet-generator

Certificates

- > Udacity Professional Web Development
- Verify at Linkedin
- > Intern2Grow Certificate Reactjs Developer
- Verify at Linkedin
- > Intern2Grow Certificate JavaScript Developer

- Verify at <u>Linkedin</u>
- > Intern2Grow Certificate Ui Developer
- Verify at <u>Linkedin</u>